<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Evers Feng Blog</title>
        <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Evers Feng Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>yf129@duke.edu (Evers)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>yf129@duke.edu (Evers)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 15:51:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Interpretable CNN: Insect Classification</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/insects_classification/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 15:51:01 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/insects_classification/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This is the post.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Life After Graduate School - Doctorate Recipient Income Analysis</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/graduate-school-dashboard/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 01:30:46 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/graduate-school-dashboard/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background Getting a doctorate degree is not only a challenging endeavor, but also an honorable one. It highlights one&rsquo;s intellectual accomplishment and is a green pass to a variety of occupations that require highly technnical skills and intensive critial thinking. For a lot of PhD candidates, the most pressing questions for them is probably how to make a good living after graduate school. In this analysis, we will look at the median income of doctorate graduate from different fields of studies in different industry.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>First 10-digit Prime in 17 pi</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/get_17_th_prime/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 15:48:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/get_17_th_prime/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What if, you just got an interview from one of your dream employers - Google, and you spent more than 10 hours a day to prepare for it. You have done everything correctly - review key data science concepts, machine learning pipeline, and get several hundred of LeetCode questions done. On the day of interview, you are asked the following question:
Give me the first 10- digit prime of the expansion in 17 * pi You paniced, get totally thrown off - I have never prepared for this kind of questions before, what do I do?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Malaria Analysis</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/visualize-malaria-data-using-altair/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 15:39:23 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/visualize-malaria-data-using-altair/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background Malaria may not be a very familiar disease to people in those more developed areas of the globe. However, at places where the climate is suitable for mosquitoes to reproduce, public health practices are most advanced and population density is high, Malaria has been a leading factor of death cases. The most horrific part about this disease that, it only takes on mosquito bite to be infected. How has the world tackled this life-threatening diseas, and what countires have made impressive progress?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Triangle Containment</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/triangle-containment/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:38:27 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/triangle-containment/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[How do you tell whether or not, a triangle drawn in a Cartesian plane contains the origin (0,0)? It is not a brain teaser as far as we can actually draw the trangle using the coordinates for its three corners, and tell from our eye whether or not it is true. But things get a little bit hard when we need to think about this algorithmically.
How to approach it? Once we connect the three corners to form a triangle, we have created a plane, in which an almost infinite number of points can be included.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Coin Sum</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/coin-sum/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:26:09 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/coin-sum/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Tricky money
Question Statement In the United Kingdom the currency is made up of pound (£) and pence (p). There are eight coins in general circulation:
1p, 2p, 5p, 10p, 20p, 50p, £1 (100p), and £2 (200p). It is possible to make £2 in the following way:
1×£1 + 1×50p + 2×20p + 1×5p + 1×2p + 3×1p How many different ways can £2 be made using any number of coins?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>10001st Prime</title>
    <link>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/10001st-prime/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:10:45 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://evers-feng.com/blogs/posts/10001st-prime/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Prime and its magic
Question Statement This question comes from Euler.com, withe question ID 7.
The original question is straightforward - how do we find the 1001st prime number among all integers?
How to approach this? First, we need to understand what the criterion for a number to be regarded as a prime number : a prime number is an integer that cannot be divded without remainder by any number except for 1 and itself.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
